{
    "id": "19830154465443a88692e41b1a8b32c5",
    "title": "Infinitives With Or Without To Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Need I ..................... the washing up?",
            "description": "When need is used as a modal auxiliary verb, it is followed by infinitive with to. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "to do",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20f7367495074c6b9a2815c5ce1655e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ....................... her what she wants.",
            "description": "Had better is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "give",
                "to give",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e96b8c5a33b34b07817f55e01ff963df"
        },
        {
            "question": "He began ......................... up off the floor.",
            "description": "The infinitive is usually used with the marker to. ",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "to get",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0509519de3ec47288e87a7dbd1526029"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do I need ......................... any longer?",
            "description": "When need is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to. ",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "to wait",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "880e9be0bdb448629715f795ea11cb64"
        },
        {
            "question": "Need I ........................... for the drinks?",
            "description": "When need is used as a modal auxiliary verb, it is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "pay",
                "to pay",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "046127ece00947a9a9cd4fb6727e4fa4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't let my children ............................ up very late.",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "stay",
                "to stay",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "95f70058b591404c86c29e132a52a7bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "They made the child .............................. the milk.",
            "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "to drink",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf8adb66b388455d9d5f76c644b94384"
        },
        {
            "question": "We both heard him ...................... that he was quitting.",
            "description": "Hear is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "say",
                "to say",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f444e1bdf51347c6aa3cb044253dd48e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you help me ............................ this radio?",
            "description": "Help can be followed by an infinitive with or without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "fix",
                "to fix",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ede966b56e384d2d84821661d66c99d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was heard ............................ that she was disappointed.",
            "description": "In passive structures, hear is followed by an infinitive with to. ",
            "answers": [
                "say",
                "to say",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0fbc9ea3b6964bd8a11c549aff4e67c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you feel the ground .............................?",
            "description": "Feel is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "shake",
                "to shake",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "949259c5c01446d08648ed6e83817932"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was made ........................ back the money.",
            "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive with to in passive structures. ",
            "answers": [
                "pay",
                "to pay",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5ff7d472672e4d5d8fc1ca865ab37063"
        }
    ]
}